Guide to the George Mason University Athletic Department records, 1979-2010
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
George Mason University Athletic Department records
1979-2010
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
George Mason University Athletic Department
R0002
14 linear feet (27 boxes)
Collection contains information relating to George Mason University athletic programs.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the George Mason University Athletic Department.
Historical Information
George Mason University has approximately 250 student-athletes compete in 20 men's and women's Division I sports-baseball, basketball, cross country, diving, golf, lacrosse, rowing, soccer, softball, swimming, tennis, indoor and outdoor track and field, volleyball, and wrestling. Intercollegiate men's and women's teams are members of the National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) Division I, the Colonial Athletic Association (CAA), the Eastern College Athletic Conference (ECAC), and the Intercollegiate Association of Amateur Athletes of America.
Scope and Content
Collection contains information relating to George Mason University athletic programs. The collection also contains news articles, tickets, fliers, and other memorabilia from the 2006 NCAA Men's Basketball Tournament.
Arrangement
Organized chronologically.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives holds the George Mason University records.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
George Mason University. Athletic Department.
Subjects:
College sports.
Contents List
- George Mason University Athletic Department records
  - Men's Basketball, 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cross Country and Track, 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cross Country Track and Field, 1980-81 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baseball, 1981-82 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cross Country Track and Field, 1981-82 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball Programs, January-February 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Monmouth 12/1/82 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Seattle 12/20/83 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Brooklyn 12/20/82 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Maryland-Eastern Shore 12/22/82 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. East Carolina 12/30/82 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Women's basketball schedule, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Cross country brochure, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Women's sports, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Soccer all star panel, October 1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Soccer brochure, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Women's soccer card, October 1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Basketball camp, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Basketball newsletter, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Basketball book, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Pamphlets, circa 1983 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Track stickers, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Patriot club, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Patriot club golf tournament, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Spuhler Field dedication, field house booklet, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Winter sports schedule, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - 2004 Spring Sports Guide (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 2003-2004 Patriots Basketball (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The OBX CAA Baseball Championship: May 15-19, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Men's Golf, 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, 1995-96 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - College Hoops Illustrated, 2003-04, Issue 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball, 1998-99 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Exciting! George Mason Basketball [no date-1980's?] (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball, 1993-94 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1991-92 Lady Patriot Basketball (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1999-2000 Golf (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1988-89 Women's Basketball (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1992-93 Basketball Magazine (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1990-91 Women's Basketball (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Women's Lacrosse-CAA Tournament Notes, April 14-16, 2000-Richmond, VA (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. William and Mary 1/8/83 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Radford 1/15/83 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Boston University 1/17/83 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Utica College 1/20/83 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. American University 1/27/83 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. University of Maine 1/29/83 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Richmond 1/31/83 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. JMU 2/16/83 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. U.S. International 3/3/83 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cross Country and Track and Field, 1982-83 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Soccer, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Davis and Elkins 12/3/83 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Long Island University 12/6/83 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. North Carolina Charlotte 1/4/84 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Monmouth 1/7/84 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. East Carolina 1/9/84 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. JMU 1/21/84 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. United States Naval Academy 1/28/84 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Towson State 1/30/84 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Richmond 2/11/84 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. North Carolina Wilmington (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Howard University 2/22/84 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. William and Mary 2/25/84 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Radford 2/27/84 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Baseball, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Women's Cross Country and Track and Field, 1983-84 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Bucknell 11/24/84 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Millersville 11/28/84 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Northern Illinois 12/4/84 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Patriot Basketball 1984-85 [Men's] (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball, 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. American University 1/2/85 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Radford University 1/12/85 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Richmond 1/16/85 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. William and Mary 1/23/85 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Morgan State 2/11/85 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. JMU 2/16/85 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Navy 2/27/85 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1985 ECAC South Conference Basketball Championship [Men's] (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Baseball, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cross Country/Track and Field, 1985-86 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball, 1985-86 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Basketball Magazine: GMU vs. Maryland 11/26/85 [Patriot Center Inaugural Edition] (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Georgetown 12/2/85 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Baseball, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Women's Soccer, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Men's Track and Field, 1986-87 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball, 1986-87 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Navy 1/12/87 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Women's Soccer, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Women's Cross Country/Track and Field, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, 1987-88 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1987-88 Women's Basketball (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Virginia Commonwealth 2/1/88 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cross Country/Track and Field, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Golf, 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Women's Soccer, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1988-89 Basketball Pre-Season Prospectus [Men's] (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball, 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1988-89 Women's Basketball Program (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Men's Cross Country/Track and Field, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Soccer, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - NCAA Basketball Championship-First and Second Rounds, 3/17 and 19/89 [Men's-See Pages 35 and 40] (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1989-90 Basketball Pre-Season Prospectus [Men's] (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball, 1989-90 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1989-90 CAA Women's Basketball Media Guide (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Santa Clara 12/9/89 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Colonial Athletic Association Men's Media Guide 1989-90 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Baseball, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Men's Cross Country and Track and Field, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Soccer, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Baseball Championships, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1990-91 25th Anniversary Basketball Season [Men's] (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - GMU Lady Patriots Basketball, 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - GMU Basketball 1990-91 Pre-Season Prospectus [Men's] (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Basketball-Reaching for New Heights, 1990 [Men's] (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. East Tennessee State 12/15/90 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Northeastern 12/19/90 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Louisville 12/22/90 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Super CAA II Hoops 1991 Richfood-Colonial Basketball Championship [Men's] (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cross Country/Track and Field, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Soccer, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Baseball, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Softball, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1991-92 GMU Basketball Magazine [Men's] (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1991-92 Women's Basketball Prospectus (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - CAA Super Hoops, Celebrating 100 Years of Basketball, 1991-92 Athletic Association Men's Basketball Media Guide (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Baseball Championships, photographs, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Baseball Championships, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Softball, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Men's Tennis, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - GMU 1992-93 Basketball Magazine [Men's]: GMU vs. Washington College (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - GMU 1992-93 Basketball Magazine [Men's]: GMU vs. UNC Wilmington (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - GMU 1992-93 Basketball Magazine [Men's]: GMU vs. Bucknell (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - GMU 1992-93 Basketball Magazine [Men's]: GMU vs. Morgan State (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1992-93 Women's Basketball Pre-Season (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball, 1992-93 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Men's Cross Country/Track and Field, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Women's Soccer, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Softball, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Tennis, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball 1993-94 Magazine: GMU vs. Troy State and GMU vs. American (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1993-94 Men's Basketball Prospectus (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 1993-94 Women's Basketball Prospectus (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Women's Basketball Photos, 1992-93 and 1993-94 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 1993-94 GMU Women's Basketball (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Baseball, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Golf, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Women's Soccer, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 1994 Softball (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Tennis, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Track and Field, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball: 1994-95 GMU vs. Old Dominion (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1994-95 Women's Basketball Prospectus (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1994-95 Women's Basketball (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - GMU Women's Basketball, 1994-95 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - GMU Patriot Club Pledge/Contribution Pamphlet 1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Colonial Athletic Association-1995 Tournament [Women's] (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Baseball, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Soccer, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Softball, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Track and Field, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Tennis, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Golf, 1995-96 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball 1995-96 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - CAA 1996 Women's Basketball Championship (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 1995-96 Basketball Magazine: GMU vs. Troy State and GMU vs. Ohio State [Men's] (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1996 Richfood Colonial Championship: Super Hoops 7 [Men's] (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Women's Soccer, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Softball, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Track and Field, 1995-96 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Tennis, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - GMU Men's Basketball Team Picture, 1996-97 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Virginia 11/30/96 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Cal Poly Slo 12/22/96 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 1996-97 GMU Basketball Schedule (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1996-97 Women's Basketball (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 1996-97 Women's Basetball Media Guide (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball 1996-97 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 1997 Baseball (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 1997 Women's Lacrosse (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Golf, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Women's Soccer, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Softball, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Tennis, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball 1997-98 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - GMU Men's Basketball 1997-98 CAA Tournament Notes (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1997-98 Women's Basketball (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Holiday Basketball Classic 1997 [Men's] (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Roster-GMU vs. UVA [no date] (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 3/12 and 14/98 NCAA Championship 1998 Division 1 Men's Basketball, East Region/Second Rounds Hosted by GMU (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1998 Baseball (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Softball, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Soccer Championships 1998-Women's Soccer (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Golf, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - GMU Women's Basketball 1998-99 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Toledo 11/24/98 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. East Carolina 2/15/99 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. American 2/20/99 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - GMU Men's Basketball-CAA Champions 1998-99 Statistics (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - GMU Men's Soccer 1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - GMU Patriot Soccer 1999 Women's (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Lacrosse, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 1999-CAA Tournaments-Women's Lacrosse (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - GMU Patriot Club Parking, 1998-99 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Golf, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Softball, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - 1998 CAA Tournament-Women's Lacrosse (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Tennis, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Women's Soccer 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Basketball Program 1999-00 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Basketball Program 1999-00 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Basketball Program 1999-00 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - GMU Men's Basketball 2000-01 Game Notes [GMU vs. JMU] (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - GMU Golf, 1999-00 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - GMU Tennis, 1999-00 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - GMU Wrestling, 1999-00 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 1999-00 Colonial Athletic Association Men's Basketball Media Guide (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - GMU Basketball 2000-01 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 2000-01 Women's Basketball (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - [Statistics, Sports Talk, Conference Schedule, etc-2001] (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Basketball Program, 2000-01 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Basketball Program, 2000-01 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Basketball Program, 2000-01 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 2001 NCAA Tournament Notes-Boise, Idaho (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - NCAA Tournament 2001-The Washington Post; Monday, March 12, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Men's 2000-01 Official NCAA Basketball Score Book (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 2001 NCAA Division 1 Men's Basketball Championship-Tournament Media Guide (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Division 1 Men's Basketball Championships 2001 NCAA [see pages 35 and 40] (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 2001 Patriot Baseball (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - OBX CAA Baseball Championship, May 2001 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 2001-02 Men's Basketball (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 2002 CAA Men's Basketball Championship [see pages 38, 64, 76, 84] (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Women's Soccer, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - GMU Patriots Basketball 2002-03 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball: GMU vs. Morehead State Eagles 11/21/03 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Wrestling, 2003-04 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 2003-04 Schedules for Men's Volleyball, Wrestling, Swimming and Diving, Men's and Women's Indoor Track and Field (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 2003-04 Men's and Women's Basketball Media Guide (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Swimming and Diving, 2003-04 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - GMU Lacrosse, 2003-04 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 2003-04 Men's Basketball Team Photos [in the woods by a lake] (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 2003-04 Men's Basketball (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball-2004 Playoffs (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Women's Lacrosse-2004 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Softball, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Track and Field, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Mason Sports, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball Tickets 12/8/04; Women's Basketball Ticket 3/10/05 (quarter finals) (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Women's Basketball, 1999-00 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Intramural Sports Participants Handbook, 1999-00 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Men's Soccer, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Women's Soccer, 1999-00 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, 2000-01 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 1999-01 Wrestling (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Women's Volleyball, 1999-00 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Tennis, 1999-01 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2000-01 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2000-01 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Men's Golf, 2000-01 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - The Colonial Athletic Association: All-Stars On The Field, All-Stars In The Classroom (ca. 2000) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball, 2000-01 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Women's Rowing, 2000-01 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Women's Softball, 2000-01 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Softball, 2000-01 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Men's Soccer, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball, 1969-1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Press Information: Baseball, 1969 and 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Sports Schedules, 1969-80 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Tennis, 1969-76 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Cross Country, 1976 and 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Men's Soccer, 1976, 1982, and 1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Track and Field, 1977-78,j 1983, 1995-96, and 1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Tennis Camp, 1980 and Basketball Camp for Girls, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Recreation and Sports Complex [Field House] (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Recreational Sports Program-Intramural Sports (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Request for NCAA Probationary Division I Status-February 16, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - GMU On The Move: October 1981, Vol. 1, No. 1 and March-April, Vol. 1, No. 6 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Patriot Club, 1982-83 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball, 1987-88, 1990-91, 1991-92, and 1996-97 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Department of Intercollegiate Athletics Intramural and Club Sports-Club Sports Handbook, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - 1996 Men's Soccer (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - 1996-98 Wrestling (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball, 1996-97 and 1997-98 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Golf, 1996-00 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Sports Schedules, 1987-88, 1996-97, and 2003 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Women's Soccer, 1996-98 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Women's Volleyball, 1996-97 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball, 1997-98 and 1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Men's Soccer, 1997-98 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Tennis, 1997-99 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Baseball, 1998-01 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball, 1998-99 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Men's Track and Field, 1998-00 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Women's Track and Field, 1998-99 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Men's Volleyball, 1998-99 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Women's Volleyball, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999-00 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999 CAA and NCAA Tournaments (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999 CAA and NCAA Tournaments (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Men's track and field, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Women's track and field, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Men's volleyball, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Men and women's basketball, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - George Evans All-American candidate (basketball), 2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Men's soccer, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Women's soccer, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Tennis, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Men's volleyball, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Women's volleyball, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Wrestling, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - The alliance, Winter 2002 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Baseball, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Men's basketball media guide, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Women's basketball media guide, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Men's soccer, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Women's soccer, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Winter and spring sports guide, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Swimming and diving, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Tickets and prices, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Men's track and field, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Women's track and field, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Men's volleyball, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Women's volleyball, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Women's volleyball, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Soccer, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Women's basketball, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Men's basketball, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Men's basketball, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Mason recreation, official guide to campus recreation, Fall 2006 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Men's and women's basketball, 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Men's basketball, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Patriot club, 2003-circa 2006 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Men's basketball, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Mason athletics, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Men's and women's soccer, women's volleyball, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Men's basketball, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Men's basketball, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Men's soccer, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Women's basketball, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Women's soccer, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Women's volleyball, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Assorted athletics, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Assorted athletics, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Assorted athletics, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Basketball, football, rowing, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Men's basketball photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Sports programs, 2000-2010 (Box 23)
- George Mason University Men's Basketball collection
  - Partners for Champions - Invitation to Join the Patriots Club 2005 (Folder 1, Box 1)
    Patriot Club brochure and application form for donations to help support Mason Athletics
  - Posters and Logos 2006 (Folder 2, Box 1)
    Basketball related flyers posted on campus.
  - Homecoming 2006 February 2006 (Folder 3, Box 1)
    2-sided postcard highlighting select activities for Homecoming 2006
  - Email Related to Men's Basketball March 2006 (Folder 4, Box 1)
    Paper printouts of emails related to Mason men's basketball. Subjects include the CHNM's Mason Basketball Digital Memory Bank, Mason faculty group pictures, Good Morning America broadcasting from Mason, and opportunities to sign a large congratulations card for the team
  - Final Four Party 2006 (Folder 5, Box 1)
    Flyers posted on campus for Final Four watch parties
  - GMU Game Day - Men and Women's Basketball Preview 2005 (Folder 6, Box 1)
    George Mason University men and women's basketball preview program featuring game schedules, stats and team profiles
  - GMU Men's Basketball - The CAA's Winningest Program Over the Past Seven Seasons 2006 (Folder 7, Box 1)
    2 sided flyer (the CAA's Winningest Program Over the Past Seven Seasons)
  - Information on Mason Web Related to Men's Basketball 2006 (Folder 8, Box 1)
    Paper printouts of George Mason University web pages regarding men's basketball
  - E-Mail from the Office of the Provost, March 29 - 30, 2006 March 29 -30, 2006 (Folder 9, Box 1)